As the temperature and humidity are important parameters in the surrounding environment, this project aims to read temperature and humidity Using DHT11 sensor. Also, using HC-06 Bluetooth module to send data read by the sensor to the Blynk App, which will offer a more human friendly interface designed by the programmer to read the data . Moreover, there will be two Led representing a feedback system. 
The feedback system will work as follows: Red Led ON if the Temperature exceeds 25,Green Led ON if Humidity exceeds 30. The readings will be updated every 30 seconds. 
